

linkedin.com/in/toddmcintire toddmcintire.com

Highly Driven Solutions Engineer with 5 year of experience in implementing and maintaining: public, private, hybrid cloud solutions, and networks. With experience in: system configuration, monitoring of Linux and windows systems, troubleshooting windows devices, servers and penetration testing.

EXPERIENCE

Network Engineer Webcom IT Solutions Apr 2017 — Dec 2017

Orlando, FL

• Maintained and repaired networks & computers for small to medium sized businesses in the central Florida area.

System Administrator

Advanced Business Networks

Apr 2019 — Mar 2020

Mundelein, IL

• Support desk for number of clients in the central and northern Illinois area. Including several Government buildings

 \bullet Personally handled all IT related requests for client WTEngineering.

System Administrator

Jul 2021 — Current

Madison, WI

Department of Veterans Affairs
• Implementation of CERNA

• T4 Security clearance

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science Full Sail University, GPA: 3.04/4.00

Aug 2015 — Jan 2017

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Operating Systems Linux/Unix, OSX, Windows

Virtualization VSphere, Proxmox

Cloud(IaaS) Amazon Web Services(AWS), Digital Ocean

Web Servers Apache, Nginx, IIS, HAProxy

 $\begin{array}{ll} \textbf{Database Systems} & \textbf{MySQL} \\ \textbf{Configuration Management} & \textbf{Ansible, Salt} \end{array}$

Programming Languages Python, C, Swift, Javascript, Rust Zabbix, Monitis, SolarWinds

Volunteer Experience

IndieBox volunteer team 2016-2016